<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dartmouth Coach</string>

    <!--Authentication-->
    <!--chooser-->
    <string name="text_email">Email</string>
    <string name="text_password">Password</string>
    <string name="button_create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="button_sign_in">Sign In</string>

    <!--Fragment Profile Request Login-->
    <string name="login_requet">You need to Login</string>
    <string name="button_login">Sign In</string>

    <!--CreateAccount-->
    <string name="radio_male">Male</string>
    <string name="radio_female">Female</string>
    <string name="radio_none">None</string>

    <string-array name="location_array">
        <item>Hanover,NH/ Dartmouth College</item>
        <item>Lebanon, NH</item>
        <item>New London, NH</item>
        <item>Boston/ Logan Airport, MA</item>
        <item>Boston/ Logan Airport, MA</item>
        <item>New York - 150 E 42nd St., NY</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="adult_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="children_array">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="discount_sdrt_content">
        Visit Boston for the day with a same-day round-trip ticket!\n\n
        Check out Dartmouth Coach’s special fare to Boston South Station:
        Child: $25 Lebanon/Hanover to Boston South Station
        Adult: $47 Lebanon/Hanover to Boston South Station\n\n
        Some restrictions apply: Same-day round-trip tickets MUST be purchased in person at the terminal on the day of travel.
        There are no black-out dates; you can travel on any day, including holidays.
        No reservations are accepted. In order to ensure yourself a seat, arrive 30 minutes before bus departure.
        A photo ID must be shown at the time of purchase. Call our Information Center at 1-800-637-0123 for more details.
    </string>

    <string name="discount_commuter_content">
        Travel to Boston South Station or Logan Airport frequently?\n\n
        Consider a 10 Ride Commuter Pass. A Commuter Pass contains ten (10) one-way tickets good for 60 days from date of purchase.
        Purchase the Commuter Pass in Lebanon, NH or Boston South Station.
        The Commuter Pass is intended for one traveler only whose name is imprinted on the ticket at the time of purchase.
        The Commuter Pass cannot be purchased for a group or multiple commuters, and is non-transferrable.
        A valid ID must be presented with ticket at time of boarding. For more information regarding these fares, call 1-800-637-0213.
    </string>

    <string name="discount_children">
        Children ride free on our Boston/Logan service!*\n\n
        Boston/Logan Service\n
        *One (1) child up to the age 14 will ride free (space permitting) on our Boston/Logan service per full paying adult ticket (one-way and roundtrip) from all Dartmouth Coach locations.
        Any additional children pay the published child’s rate*.\n\n
        New York City Service\n
        One (1) child up to the age 15 will ride for 1/2 of the adult fare per full paying adult ticket (one-way and round-trip). Any additional
        children pay the full published adult rate.  Children under 16 are not permitted to travel alone.
    </string>

</resources>
